[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
"Kiss Or Kill"
(Episode 7)
Listen to me.
I'm his brother.
Brother?
What are you laughing at?
At how naive you are.
The ones who do this to you
are your own brothers.
You still think it's funny?
Don't be afraid.
After all, you're Brother
Yan's good friend.
I won't hurt you.
This is just a little something
to help you loosen your tongue.
It's good stuff.
Second Uncle.
Even though the drug didn't work,
we still can't trust this guy.
Black Scorpion,
before the deal with the
Black Moon Society is done,
you can't touch A-yan.
And Nie Chuan can't die either.
Why not?
Second Uncle, we've been running
that route for years,
and it gets shut down just like that.
As soon as Nie Chuan shows up,
a new route magically appears.
Don't you think that's
a little too convenient?
The military route got cut off.
You can't blame that on him.
Besides, he has a new route in his hands.
If it's useful, we keep him around for now.
As for whether he's friend or foe,
what's the rush?
Second Uncle,
I'm just worried that you...
You don't need to worry about this.
Send your men
to look into Nie Chuan's background.
The more detailed, the better.
Yes, Second Uncle.
Time to eat.
It still hurts. I can't stand up.
Eat.
My hands hurt too. I can't lift them.
Feed me.
As long as you're not
afraid I'll poison you.
It's your first time cooking?
Tastes pretty good.
Even food can't shut you up.
Who is it?
You little bastard.
I've dug up everything on you this time.
Not this again.
You used to be in the government army.
You were kicked out for insubordination,
and that's why you became a mercenary.
Right?
You work fast, Brother Scorpion.
That's right.
I did.
So what?
You knew?
I knew.
You knew and you still trust him this much?
I don't.
That's why after the
incident with the shipment,
I've been investigating too.
And now I have evidence in my hands.
It's much more useful
than what you found.
I was just about to take
him to see Second Uncle.
Want to come along?
Second Uncle.
I checked the surveillance footage.
The night before the delivery,
A-feng went into the warehouse.
What were you doing there?
I... I was just doing an inspection.
Since when do you have the authority
to inspect Second Uncle's goods?
Black Scorpion,
he's your man.
What should we do?
Brother Scorpion, please do
something, Brother Scorpion!
Second Uncle,
A-feng has been with me for years.
He couldn't have...
Second Uncle,
I didn't do anything!
I swear,
I didn't ask what you did.
I asked what we should do.
Brother Scorpion!
Please, you have to save me!
Whatever Second Uncle says,
goes.
I didn't do anything!
It was Scor... Scor...
Lin Yan.
I'm having a harder time figuring you out.
You've got another life on your hands.
What else was I supposed to do?
Send you to your death?
You set A-feng up.
First, you made Black Scorpion think
you had something to hide.
The more you tried to hide it,
the more he wanted to dig.
A-feng was obedient enough,
and stupid enough.
Now dead men tell no tales.
When the evidence was presented,
Black Scorpion had no
choice but to shut up.
He couldn't exactly
tell Lin Cang to his face
that he wanted to help you.
Lin Yan,
you're really something else.
Do you still dare to stay?
In this world,
not many people would
use themselves as bait.
Take a guess if I dare.
Stop wading into these muddy waters.
We were never on the
same path to begin with.
I can be.
I won't let the person I like lose.
Don't make promises so easily.
If I say it,
I'll definitely do it.
From today on,
count me in.
You don't belong here.
Good thing I don't plan on leaving.
Okay, got it.
Coward.
Second Uncle.
Black Moon has replied.
The deal is still on.
For the security this time,
you'll be in full charge.
I'll have Nie Chuan coordinate the route.
We're not using his route.
Then...
Which route are we taking?
You don't need to worry about the route.
You just need to ensure the site is secure
during the transaction.
Which warehouse will the goods leave from?
Any information you need to know,
I will tell you.
As for everything else,
don't ask.
Yes.
A-yan,
don't let me down.
The Black Moon Society agreed
to continue the deal so quickly.
Something's not right.
You think so too?
There was a problem with the last shipment.
Any normal buyer
would be suspicious.
But they're rushing to
close the deal instead.
Either
their demand is
more urgent than we thought,
or
they're planning something big.
It could be a national-level war.
This deal cannot go through.
What do you mean?
This route is wrong.
The terrain is too flat.
It's wide open on both sides.
If we're ambushed, there's nowhere to hide.
Then where do you think
they'll go?
You knew about this route all along.
Lin Cang put me in charge of security,
but won't let me touch the route.
He gave up on your route.
He doesn't trust you.
No.
It's because your route is too clean.
Too perfect.
Every single checkpoint
is timed perfectly.
Every inspection station
is bypassed cleanly.
A perfect route
is the most suspicious route.
And Lin Cang
doesn't believe in perfection.
Do you?
I believe in you.
Brother Yan,
Father only wants you to go in alone.
Why is Brother Yan so good to you?
Maybe because I'm just that good.
He's never brought an outsider back before.
Don't drag him down.
I traded my life for his.
I'm more afraid of him
getting hurt than you are.
Even truth serum doesn't work on you.
You're no ordinary person.
I'm just a middleman.
Just making a quick buck.
Thank you, Second Uncle.
A-yan.
Is everything arranged?
Yes.
Black Scorpion.
Have your men
assist with security this time.
A-yan will be in charge
of deploying all personnel.
Second Uncle.
I've always managed my own men.
This time is different.
The deal is crucial.
We can't afford any slip-ups.
A-yan is in charge of the site.
Your men will take orders from him.
It'll be much more efficient this way.
But...
Are you questioning my arrangements?
I wouldn't dare.
Then it's settled.
You can go now.
I still have things to discuss with A-yan.
A-yan.
I need you to keep a
close eye on this deal.
As for Black Scorpion's men,
use them as you see fit.
Replace anyone who doesn't follow orders.
We can't have another incident like A-feng.
Understood.
Understood. Go on.
Oh, right.
Once you're tired of your toys,
dispose of them cleanly.
Don't let them interfere
with our real business.
Yes.
I'll pay a visit in person.
There definitely won't
be any issues this time.
Rest assured.
Got it, got it.
Second Uncle just said,
I can use your men as I see fit.
If they don't follow orders,
I should replace them.
Are you questioning my arrangements?
I just think
you've followed Second
Uncle for so many years,
you shouldn't be treated like this.
Brother Scorpion!
Brother Scorpion, save me!
Second Uncle! Brother
Scorpion! Brother Scorpion!
A-feng has been with me for a long time.
He's heading out.
Where to?
Before he left,
I heard him take a call.
He sounded very cautious.
There aren't many people
who can make him act that way.
Over the years, your goods
have always found a way out.
Everything has been smooth sailing.
Does really no one know
who's backing him?
He never lets anyone
get close to that information.
I've investigated for years,
but I still have no idea
who the mastermind is.
This is the first time
we have a chance to tail him.
It seems it's not just the Black Moon
Syndicate that's anxious this time.
He's anxious too.
Or rather,
the person backing him is anxious.
If
he's going to meet
the person on the phone,
then that means
this person
is the real power
behind Lin Cang.
Are you coming along?
Obviously.
Alright.
Let's switch cars.
Mine is too flashy.
Looks like this is the place.
Yeah.
He noticed us.
Don't move.
Follow my lead.
Just a couple of lovebirds.
They're gone.
You're getting bolder by the minute.
Stop messing around.
Let's get down to business.
This is exactly the business
I want to get down to.
You really don't know
how to prioritize, do you?
I know my priorities all too well.
That's why I waited until now.
The priority right now is
figuring out who Lin Cang went
to such great lengths to meet.
Song Peng.
Song Peng?
Deputy Minister of Defense?
This is the secret rendezvous spot
General Song Peng gave to his mistress.
I've been here before.
You've been here?
I had a mission before
that required me to get acquainted
with General Song Peng's mistress.
Right here.
Acquainted?
A mission?
How did you get acquainted?
Dressed up as a plumber?
Played the hero saving
the damsel in distress? Or...
I don't rely on those
cheap tricks.
So you're saying
you spent a romantic
night with this mistress?
Not exactly.
Something came up,
and I was called away.
What a pity.
Where are we going?
To change clothes.
It's too far to go back to your place.
Let's just rest here for now.
We'll figure it out tomorrow.
You used to live here?
One of them.
Seems like you have quite a few hideouts.
I know what you're thinking.
I don't care who's backing him
or how powerful they are.
As long as he's in your way,
I have ways to make him disappear.
But this power
is beyond what we previously imagined.
Song Peng.
Deputy Minister of Defense. A general.
Don't underestimate me.
Who knows,
I might be able to help you
much more than you think.
I know you're capable.
If you wanted to,
you could take Lin Cang's life at any time.
But even if Lin Cang dies,
as long as Song Peng is still around,
there will be a second Lin Cang tomorrow.
And a third.
Then...
will you be the next Lin Cang?
No.
Then there you have it.
As long as it's not you,
I'll kill all the rest.